Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 4 and District 4 Locals, 1935-1991 UE.4.1.4
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 4, 1.
  - District 4 Outgoing Correspondence, March 11, 1937-March 2, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Leo Grossman to Carey Regarding Emerson Radio, Dismissal and NLRB, March 11, 1937; 18.
    - Francis Gulotta to Emspak Regarding Women, Wages and African Americans, April 21, 1953; 19.
    - Gulotta to All Local Presidents Regarding Jersey City Westinghouse Strike with Report on Monies Collected for the Westinghouse Strike and Weekly Account of Expenses for UE 456 Westinghouse Strike, March 2, 1956; 20.
  - District 4 Outgoing Correspondence, December 7, 1936-May 29, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Clifford Haley to Julius Emspak Regarding Machine and Instrument Council, May 8, 1940; 1.
    - John Harett to James Carey Regarding Radio Broadcasts, December 7, 1936; 2.
    - Harett to Emspak Regarding M.W. Kellogs Organization, December 12, 1936; 3.
    - Tracy Hartwell to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, March 30, 1945; 4.
    - Herbert Hirschberg to Emspak Regarding Finances and Locals 409 and 420, November 11, 1944; 5.
    - Marian Hislop to Emspak Regarding World War II and Second Front, May 19, 1943; 6.
    - Sam Ingram to UE Regarding Staff Finances, December 2, 1946; 7.
    - Mariba Kaufman to Carey Regarding Women's Auxiliary, January 25, 1940; 8.
    - Walter Kaufman to Carey Regarding Organization, 9.
    - Tobias Kippler to Carey Regarding Organization, April 15, 1937; 10.
    - Dorothy Kingsley to Emspak Regarding Victor Metal Strike with June 14, 1937, Albert Stonkus Letter, July 1937; 11.
    - Mary Knowles to James Matles Regarding Education and Women, May 19, 1942; 12.
    - Knowles to Presidents of All New York Locals Regarding WWII and Sports with Leaflet, June 11, 1942; 13.
    - Knowles to Matles Regarding Local 1225 Membership Meeting, July 1, 1942; 14.
    - Knowles to UE Officers Regarding UE Officers, September 15, 1942; 15.
    - Knowles to National Officers Regarding District 4 Annual Ball, October 7, 1942; 16.
    - Alfreda Kolyinski to Janet Regarding RCA Organization, May 15, 1945; 17.
    - Kolylinski to Janet Regarding Staff Finances, May 29, 1945; 18.
    - James Kotter to UE Regarding Political Action, April 21, 1940; 19.
    - Gertrude Lowe to Emspak Regarding 1939 UE Convention, August 3, 1939; 20.
    - Bev Lewis to UE Regarding Electric Light Industry Organization, September 29, 1937; 21.
  - District 4 Outgoing Correspondence, May 1937-November 1957 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Robert Logsdon to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee Factionalism, March 29, 1945; 1.
    - Charles MacLaren to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Phelps Dodge Strikes, July 12, 1946; 2.
    - William Magee to Emspak Regarding Queens Labor Rally, May 13, 1943; 3.
    - Magee to Fitzgerald Regarding Queens Political Action, May 13, 1943; 4.
    - Magee to James Matles Regarding Queens Political Action, May 18, 1943; 5.
    - S. Mason to Matles Regarding Supplies, November 12, 1937; 6.
    - Mason to Matles Regarding Organizers Bulletin, October 26, 1937; 7.
    - Harry McCabe to James Carey Regarding Electricians Organization, November 28, 1938; 8.
    - William Mitchell to Emspak Regarding Local 411 Star Porcelain Strike, May 1937; 9.
    - Mitchell to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 1222, 1223 and 1230, May 4, 1939; 10.
    - Harold Moore to Matles Regarding Mailing List, November 20, 1957; 11.
    - Frank Murphy to Fitzgerald Regarding District 4 Dance, March 2, 1951; 12.
    - Carl Nelson to UE Regarding Finances and Mailing List, April 12, 1941; 13.
    - William Newman to Carey Regarding Unemployment, January 3, 1939; 14.
    - Newman to Matles Regarding Unemployment, January 3, 1939; 15.
    - Newman to Emspak Regarding Medical Projects, July 14, 1938; 16.
    - John Paul to Emspak Regarding Kelly Press Organization, June 28, 1937; 17.
    - Jack Penberthy to Emspak Regarding Bloomfield Political Action, March 5, 1943; 18.
    - W.J. Peters to UE Regarding Lidgerwood, October 23, 1942; 19.
    - Peters to UE Regarding Organization, November 8, 1942; 20.
    - Peters to UE Regarding Supplies and Insurance, March 10, 1943; 21.
    - Sol Potegal to Carey Regarding District 12 Dance, September 28, 1937; 22.
    - Potegal to Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 5, 1937; 23.
    - Potegal to Matles Regarding 1942 Bayonne Council and UE Convention, July 23, 1942; 24.
  - District 4 Outgoing Correspondence, March 1936-October 1949 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - John Pollock to James Matles Regarding Education, November 6, 1937; 1-2.
    - Pollock to Matles Regarding Education and Organization, November 20, 1937; 3.
    - Pollock to Mr. Seed Regarding Education and Finances, November 27, 1937; 4.
    - Pollock to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, December 13, 1937; 5.
    - Pollock to Emspak Regarding Strikes and Constitution, March 31, 1938; 6.
    - Israel Purr to James Carey Regarding Inflation and Political Action, March 21, 1940; 7.
    - Floyd Raul to Emspak Regarding Local 408 Finances, March 24, 1938; 8.
    - Charles Rivers to Emspak, October 27, 1937; 9.
    - Steve Rubicki to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 21, 1936; 10.
    - Rubicki to Emspak Regarding Hamson RCA Organization, July 11, 1936; 11.
    - Rubicki to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 15, 1936; 12.
    - Ben Riskin to Fred Livingston Regarding Staff Finances, April 28, 1944; 13.
    - Tony Salese to David Ratner, October 1949; 14.
    - William Santora to Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 10, 1943; 15.
    - Santora to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, November 22, 1944; 16.
    - Sanotra to Matles Regarding Local 448 Finances and Amalgamation, August 26, 1949; 17.
    - Louis Sarti to William Mitchell Regarding Local 1206 Clarostat Collective Bargaining, May 27, 1938; 18.
    - Marcel Scherer to Emspak Regarding White Collar Workers, Wages and War Labor Board, October 8, 1944; 19.
    - Scherer to Emspak Regarding African Americans, Unemployment and Seniority, October 9, 1944; 20.
    - Scherer to Paul Saymour Regarding Reconversion and Small Business, July 5, 1945; 21.
    - Scherer to Sirs Regarding Phelps Dodge and Anaconda Strikes, February 26, 1946; 22.
    - Scherer to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Yonkers Political Action, March 4, 1946; 23.
    - Scherer to Matles Regarding General Radio and Television Organization, North American Phillips and Runaway Shops, April 30, 1946; 24.
    - Scherer to David Scribner Regarding Local 428 Sonotone Contract and Union Shops, September 9, 1946; 25.
  - District 4 Outgoing Correspondence, June 18, 1937-August 2, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Marcel Scherer to UE Regarding Finances, October 3, 1946; 1.
    - Scherer to James Matles Regarding Wages and Stewards Conference, December 26, 1946; 2.
    - Scherer to Matles Regarding Trenton, January 17, 1947; 3.
    - Scherer to Edward Matthews Regarding Westinghouse White Collar Workers Organization, October 28, 1947; 4.
    - Scherer to Peter Abbondi Regarding Westinghouse Wages and White Collar Workers, November 20, 1947; 5.
    - Scherer to Richard Lynch Regarding Bloomfield Westinghouse Unemployment and White Collar Workers, July 2, 1948; 6.
    - Scherer to Matthews Regarding Bendix Collective Bargaining, August 2, 1948; 7.
    - Frank Schmitt to James Carey Regarding United Razor Workers, September 26-October 13, 1938; 8-10.
    - Schmitt to Carey Regarding United Razor Workers with December 17, 1938, Letter to W. Smethurst, December 19, 1938; 11.
    - Max Schroeder to UE Regarding District 12, June 18, 1937; 12.
    - Schroeder to Brothers Regarding District 4 Executive Board, September 22, 1937; 13.
    - Cecilia Shone to General Executive Board Regarding Local 1226 Prestolock Strike, Runaway Shops and Holob Trial with Resolution, March 25, 1938; 14.
    - Domenic Sieni to Wiliam Mitchell Regarding Employment, July 19, 1938; 15.
    - Jack Simon to Julius Emspak Regarding Education and Literature, August 26, 1946; 16.
    - Simon to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Bloomfield and Education, November 26, 1946; 17.
    - Simon to Emspak Regarding Education and Literature, December 12, 1946; 18.
  - District 4 Outgoing Correspondence, April 10, 1937-March 23, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Jack Simon to David Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, June 1947; 1-2.
    - Simon to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, 1947; 3.
    - William Smith to Brothers Regarding District Council Meeting, March 23, 1953; 4.
    - Frederick Smith to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Constitution and Stewards, August 25, 1943; 5.
    - Walter Speicher to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues and Check-off, November 20, 1946; 6.
    - Al Stearn to James Matles Regarding North Adams, May 18, 1938; 7.
    - Stearn to Matles Regarding Yonkers and Plainfield Organization, May 24, 1938; 8.
    - Stearn to Matles Regarding Aerovor Wages, May 25, 1938; 9.
    - Stearn to Matles Regarding North Adams Sprague Organization, July 28, 1939; 10.
    - Edward Steward to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 15, 1941; 11.
    - Steward to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board and Finances, December 30, 1942-February 2, 1943; 12-13.
    - Steward to Matles Regarding WLB, February 2, 1943; 14.
    - Steward to All Local Financial Secretaries Regarding Officers, February 8, 1943; 15.
    - Steward to Ratner Regarding Finances and Organization, July 11, 1946; 16.
    - Steward to Barish Regarding Finances, October 9, 1947; 17.
    - Alexander Stroll to Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 16, 1937; 18.
    - Myles Travers to Emspak Regarding Steel Workers Organizing Committee, April 10-20, 1937; 19-20.
    - Travers to Emspak Regarding Gem Razor Organization, May 5, 1937; 21-22.
  - District 4 Outgoing Correspondence, February 22, 1938-May 22, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - James Trenz to Ed Matthews Regarding Local 1227, February 28, 1950; 1.
    - William Wallace to Sisters Regarding Local 1227 Waldes, October 3, 1951; 2.
    - Wallace to Ernest DeMaio Regarding UE Fighting Fund, November 21, 1951; 3.
    - Wallace to Carl Manzuni Regarding Finances, May 22, 1953; 4.
    - Rebecca Weiner to UE Regarding Premier Crystal, March 23, 1943; 5.
    - Alf Wishart to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization and Finances, February 22, 1938; 6.
    - Len Zaleski to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 31, 1944; 7.
    - William Zeman to UE, April 15, 1940; 8.
    - Evelyn Zucherman to UE Regarding Staff Finances, January 13, 1945; 9.
    - Unsigned Letter to James Matles Regarding Local 1227, Finances and Membership Drive, March 28, 1938; 10.
  - District 4 Correspondence, January 30-February 10, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - District 4 Correspondence, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - District 4 Correspondence, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - District 4 Correspondence, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - District 4 Correspondence, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - District 4 Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - District 4 Correspondence, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - District 4 Correspondence, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - District 4 Correspondence, August 12, 1968-December 17, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - District 4 Patterson, New Jersey, Organizing Committee Correspondence, May 18, 1963-January 19, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - District 4 Financial Vouchers, April 1944-June 1954 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - District 4 Salary Expense Letters, May 5, 1941-October 29, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Carl Nelson, May 5, 1941; 1.
    - James McLeish, December 29, 1942; 2.
    - Michael Gladstone, May 17-29, 1943; 3-4.
    - Otis Mumma, May 31, 1943; 5.
    - Irving Anthony, May 31-June 11, 1943; 6-7.
    - Mumma, June 11, 1943; 8.
    - Anthony, June 30, 1943; 9.
    - Mumma, June 30-July 14, 1943; 10-11.
    - Anthony, July 29, 1943; 12.
    - Mumma, July 29-August 13, 1943; 13-14.
    - Anthony, August 13-31, 1943; 15-16.
    - Mumma, August 3-September 15, 1943; 17-18.
    - Anthony, September 15-29, 1943; 19-20.
    - Mumma, September 29-October 14, 1943; 21-22.
    - Richard Townsend, October 29, 1943; 23.
    - Mumma, October 29, 1943; 24.
  - District 4 Salary Expense Letters, December 14, 1943-June 28, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Otis Mumma, December 14-29, 1943; 1-2.
    - Evelyn Zuckerman, July 5-December 28, 1944; 3-11.
    - Marcene Doyle, January 12-February 1, 1945; 12-13.
    - Tracey Hartwell, March 29-April 27, 1945; 14-16.
    - Alfreda Kobylinski, May 22, 1945; 17.
    - Hartwell, May 28-June 28, 1945; 18-20.
  - District 4 Supply Requests, March 1, 1944-March 24, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - District 4 Financial, December 29, 1943-May 7, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Disbursment Voucher, December 29, 1943; 1.
    - Bill, May 20, 1946; 2.
    - Legal Bills Regarding Local 426, February 24, 1947; 3.
    - Defense Fund Report, October 1, 1948; 4.
    - Supply Form, June 1952; 5.
    - Organizational Expenses, June 21, 1954; 6.
    - Outstanding Bills, June 21, 1954; 7.
    - Supplementary Report on Otis, March 1952; 8.
    - Per Capita Tax, 9.
    - Salaries, 10.
    - People's Press Bills, 11.
  - District 4 Battery Workers Conference, November 7, 1943-April 2, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Minutes with November 20, 1942, Peter Besch Letter to All Locals, November 7-9, 1942; 1.
    - Besch to All Locals with Registration Forms, Questionnaire and Agenda, April 2, 1943; 2.
  - District 4 Battery Workers Conference Minutes with Delegate List; Approximate Wage Increase; Labor's Part in Nutrition; Addresses by Leonard Kagen; and Address on Lead Poisoning, May 15-17, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - District 4 Legislative Conference, February 21, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Julius Emspak Speech Notes, February 21, 1943; 1.
    - Call to Action with February 10, 1943, James McLeish Letter to All Organizers, February 1943; 2.
    - Emspak Speech, February 21, 1943; 3.
  - District 4 Legislative Conference, February 28, 1943-May 10, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Program, February 28, 1943; 1.
    - Legislative Report, 1951; 2.
    - Eastern Seaboard Legislative Conference, May 10, 1952; 3.
  - District 4 Conventions, June 12, 1937-January 21, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Minutes with Ernest Arvidson Letter to Julius Emspak, June 12, 1937; 1.
    - James McLeish to Albert Fitzgerald with Convention Call, January 21, 1944; 2.
  - District 4 Convention Minutes, February 6, 1944-October 26, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - District 4 Westinghouse Conference, November 9, 1940-June 1, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Minutes, November 9, 1940, May 4, 1944; 1-2.
    - Minutes with Resolution, June 1, 1944; 3.
  - District 4 Stewards Conference Proceedings, January 25, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - District 4 Stewards Conferences, June 1947-November 1951 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Conference Call with June 5, 1947, James McLeish Letter to All Secretaries, June 1947; 1.
    - Minutes with Political Action Statement and Fight Against the Taft-Hartley Bill, June 26, 1947; 2.
    - Conference Call, November 18, 1951; 3.
  - District 4 Local Conference Minutes, October 31, 1939, June 27, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - District 4 Conference, March 1940-February 1949 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Machine and Instrument Shop Conference Program with March 7, 1940, James Lustig Letters to Julius Emspak and James Matles, March 1940; 1.
    - Prodcution for Victory Conference Regarding Call, May 1942; 2.
    - Veterans and Service Men Welfare Conference, January 19, 1945; 3.
    - Meeting of General Electric and Westinghouse Local Presidents Minutes, April 28, 1948; 4.
    - Womens Conference Proceedings, February 5, 1949; 5.
  - District 4 Conference, February 1948-July 1949 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Wage Conference Proceedings, February 5, 1948; 1.
    - District 1 and District 4 Unemployment Conference, July 1949; 2.
  - District 4 Conference, June 1950-September 1954 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Peace Conference Proceedings, June 1950; 1.
    - Health and Welfare Conference Call with February 26, 1954, James McLeish Letter to Brothers and March 1, 1954, McLeish Letter to James Matles, April 3, 1954; 2.
    - Fair Practice Conference Call, September 18, 1954; 3.
  - District 4 Officers Annual Report, September 1937-August 1938 (Box 3, Folder 44-45)
  - District 4 Officers Reports, May 20, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - District 4 Officers Reports, September 1937-August 1938 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - District 4 Officers Reports, October 21, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - District 4 Officers Reports, October 27, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - District 4 Officers Reports, October 26, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - District 4 Officers Reports, October 24, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - District 4 Officers Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - District 4 Officers Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - District 4 Reports to UE, June 1938-December 1943 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - District 4 Reports to UE, April 1-November 1, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - District 4 Convention Resolutions, July 22, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - District 4 Convention Resolutions, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - District 4 Convention Resolutions, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - District 4 Convention Resolutions, August 14, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - District 4 Convention Resolutions, August 6, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - District 4 Convention Resolutions, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - District 4 Carrier Call Strike, December 5-7, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Alex Rauch to UE, December 5, 1936; 1.
    - Carrier Call Committees, December 7, 1936; 2.
  - District 4 Cable Industry Organization, March 5-20, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Michael Ritondo to John Lewis, March 5, 1937; 1.
    - Lewis to Ritondo, March 16, 1937; 2.
    - John Brophy to Ritondo, March 20, 1937; 3.
  - District 4 Newark Organization, February 18-April 9, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Abraham Wasserman to Julius Emspak, February 18, 1937; 1.
    - Emspak to Wasserman, April 9, 1937; 2.
  - District 4 Berger Employment, August 30-31, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Fred Berger to UE, August 30, 1938; 1.
    - Julius Emspak to Berger, August 31, 1938; 2.
  - District 4 Local 1209 Finances, August 25-September 16, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Nathan Rosenberg to James Carey, August 25, 1938; 1.
    - Julius Emspak to Rosenberg, September 16, 1938; 2.
  - District 4 Wages and Hours, October 18-20, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Philip Walfish to UE, October 18, 1938; 1.
    - William Mitchell to Walfish, October 20, 1938; 2.
  - District 4 Newark Lamp Organization, January 4-6, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Julius Emspak to W.R. Burrows, January 4, 1939; 1.
    - Burrows to Emspak, January 6, 1939; 2.
  - District 4 Action Yarns, January 14-March 3, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Philip Dodge to James Carey, January 14-February 6, 1939; 1-2.
    - Carey to Dodge, February 20, 1939; 3.
    - Dodge to Carey, March 3, 1939; 4.
  - District 4 Sturis Employment, January 23-25, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - John Sturis to Congress of Industrial Organizations, January 23, 1939; 1.
    - Summary, January 24, 1939; 2.
    - Walter Smethurst to James Carey, January 25, 1939; 3.
  - District 4 General Electric Service Organization, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Memo, 1939; 1.
    - James Matles to Al Stearn, July 25, 1939; 2.
  - District 4 Metal Workers Organization, September 12-15, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Stephen Bedell to Allan Haywood, September 12, 1939; 1.
    - Pete Mosele to James Carey, September 14, 1939; 2.
    - James Matles to Bedell, September 15, 1939; 3.
  - District 4 Paramount Electric Organization, February 19-March 4, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - George Ahrens to Congress of Industrial Organizations, February 19, 1940; 1.
    - Allan Haywood to James Carey, February 27, 1940; 2.
    - Carey to Ahrens, March 4, 1940; 3.
  - District 4 John Dewey Society, July 25-31, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Alice Hanson to James Carey, July 25, 1940; 1.
    - Carey to Ruth Young, July 31, 1940; 2.
  - District 4 Habirshaw Organizing Drive and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, March 27, 1940-May 10, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Mailing List, March 27, 1940; 1.
    - Ed McAlinn to Edward Podlewski, May 29, 1940; 2.
    - UE Letter to Habirshaw Cable, June 7, 1940; 3.
    - James Matles to Wylie Brown, June 26, 1940; 4.
    - UE to All Habirshaw Workers, October 22, 1940; 5.
    - IBEW Shop Committee to IBEW Members, October 1940; 6.
    - Brown to Habirshaw Employees, December 12, 1940; 7.
    - UE Statement, December 1940; 8.
    - Neal McGillicuddy Letter, May 10, 1941; 9.
    - UE to McAllin, 10.
    - List of Card Signers, 11.
  - District 4 National Labor Relations Board Conference, December 31, 1940-January 16, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - L. Hamilton Garner to James Carey, December 31, 1940; 1.
    - Carey to Garner, January 16, 1941; 2.
  - District 4 Organizating Reports, February 18-July 11, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - District 4 Organizers Weekly Reports, May 7-15, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Report, May 7, 1943; 1.
    - Michael Gladstone, May 8-15, 1943; 2-3.
  - District 4 Local 419 Factionalism, John Gannon to James Matles, May 28-June 27, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - District 4 Railway Express Organization, September 12-19, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Hyman Blume to UE, September 12, 1945; 1.
    - Ray Klausner to Blume, September 19, 1945; 2.
  - District 4 Staff Assignments, September 22-October 1, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - District 4 Survey of Shops, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - District 4 Organizers Weekly Reports, Michael Witkosky, January 25-February 8, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - District 4 Sperry Gyro Job Evaluations, July 29-September 16, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Meeting Between Member of Turret Lathe Department and UE Officials, July 29, 1947; 1.
    - Henry Johnson to Julius Emspak, September 6, 1947; 2.
    - Memo with Turret Lathe Operatiors List, September 6, 1947; 3.
    - Job Description, 4.
    - Operation Sketch Ticket, 5.
    - Emspak to James McLeish, September 16, 1947; 6.
  - District 4 Labor Extension Bill Contest, November 25-December 3, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Contest Outline, 1.
    - Hilda Smith to Albert Fitzgerald, November 25, 1947; 2.
    - Press Release, December 2, 1947; 3.
    - Fitzgerald to James McLeish, December 2, 1947; 4.
    - Smith to Fitzgerald, December 3, 1947; 5.
  - District 4 Secessions, February 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "The Secession Plot of the Members of Democratic Action" with February 18, 1948, Albert Fitzgerald Memo to James McLeish and February 13, 1948, McLeish Letter to Brothers, February 1948; 1.
    - Memo with February 19, 1948, McLeish Letter, February 1948; 2.
  - District 4 Taft-Hartley Affidavits, March 1-2, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Thomas Keenan to UE, March 1, 1948; 1.
    - George Keenan to UE, March 1, 1948; 2.
    - Albert Fitzgerald to G. Keenan, March 2, 1948; 3.
  - District 4 Political Action Committee, March-May 1948 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Charles Berlin to Albert Fitzgerald, March 1948; 1.
    - Memo with May, 3, 1948, Ruth Young Letter to Fitzgerald, May 1948; 2.
  - District 4 Special Organizational Reports, July 24-August 7, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Harry Kelner, July 24, 1948; 1.
    - James Lustig, August 6, 1948; 2.
    - Marcel Scherer, August 7, 1948; 3.
  - District 4 Mario Russo Memorial Fund Reports, December 31, 1948-December 31, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - District 4 James Lustig Legal Briefs, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Leaflet Excerpt, 1949; 1.
    - House Un-American Activities Committee Excerpt, 1949; 2.
    - Dockets Excerpt, 1949; 3.
    - HUAC Hearing, 1949; 4-8.
    - Leaflet Excerpt, 1949; 9.
    - HUAC Hearings Excerpt, 1949; 10.
  - District 4 James Lustig Legal Briefs, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)